# ChenYu Geng

972-697-9502 · cgeng.charlie@gmail.com 620 w westchester pkwy, Grand Prairie, TX

Portfolio: https://www.chenyug.com

# FRONT-END DEVELOPER/DESIGNER

- I am currently a graduate student who studies Information Technology and Management at DBU and will graduate in December 2023.
- I am a skilled Front-End Developer with experience in creating dynamic and user-friendly websites. My
  expertise lies in HTML, CSS, JavaScript and design with Figma. I have a strong understanding of UI/UX
  design principles and an eye for detail, which enables me to create visually appealing and responsive
  web pages. I am familiar with software development process, Agile development.

#### **SKILLS**

HTML/CSSWordPressGit/GithubJavaScriptChatGPTFigmaReact.jsSQL/NoSQLPython

### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Dallas Baptist University IT Department Dallas, TX Customer Relationship Management Assistant 2023.01 - Present

Use Salesforce and Informatica to load data and manage applications.

BigBang Artwork, Remote WordPress developer

2021.12 - 2023.01

Accomplishments:

- Use WordPress to build the website from 0 to 1.
- Design and implement UI and functionality of the website.
- · Use Plugins in WordPress to manage the user system.
- · Website: https://www.bigbangartwork.org

LeZhu Network Technology Co. XuZhou, China Software internship

2019.06 - 2019.09

Accomplishments:

- Learned about the software development process in a team
- · Participated in the development of WeChat applets
- · Helped team make database queries and software testing

## **EDUCATION EXPERIENCE**

Dallas Baptist University

Master in Information Technology and Management

2021 - Present

Current GPA: 3.953

------

Dallas Baptist University
BAS in Computer Information Science

2020 - 2022

GPA: 3.903